<records>
<record type="CT" order_item="CT Head">
Clinical Details

Report

CT Head : Noncontrast study. No previous CT for comparison.

There is increased attenuation seen within the distal left terminal carotid artery and proximal portion of the left middle cerebral artery consistent with acute thrombus. Subtle sulcal effacement is noted in the left MCA territory, particularly around the peri-Sylvian parenchyma.

Impression:

Evolving left MCA infarction. No acute haemorrhage seen. Generalised atrophy and is evidence of some diffuse low density change within the cerebral white matter which would be in keeping with small vessel cerebrovascular ischaemia.
</record>
<record type="CT" order_item="CT Head">
Clinical Details

Report

No previous brain imaging for comparison.

Cerebral involutional change, advanced for age.  Evidence of an old left posterior temporal/parietal infarct.  White matter hypoattenuation in keeping with moderate small vessel change.  No intracranial mass, infarct or haemorrhage.  The skull vault and skull base appear unremarkable.

Opinion:

Advanced cerebral atrophy, moderate small vessel disease and old infarcts as described above. No acute intracranial finding.

</record>
<record type="CT" order_item="CT Head With/Without Contrast">
Clinical Details

Report

CT HEAD PRE AND POST CONTRAST:

Comparison is made with the previous CT examination of xxxxxxxxxx.

Pre-contrast study shows focal areas of hyperattenuation in the anterior left frontal lobe, in the left corona radiata and within the centrum semi-ovale on the left, new since the previous CT.  There are minimal white matter changes around the anterior left frontal lesion. Small chronic left convexity subdural collection.  Small quantity of subarachnoid blood in left frontal sulcus.  Moderate small vessel disease.  No extra-axial collections.  Normal ventricles and basal cisterns.  Skull vault normal. Contrast images show no evidence of abnormal enhancement.

Opinion:

Multiple foci of acute haemorrhage in the left frontal lobe, trace of subarachnoid blood and shallow left subdural haemorrhage. No evidence of cerebral metastases.

</record>
<record type="CT" order_item="CT Head">
Clinical Details

Report

Comparison made with the previous CT scan from xxxxxxxxxx.

Unenhanced CT brain.

Established right parietal subcortical gliosis, unchanged since the previous scan. Several patchy white matter low density areas within the corona radiata as well as at the periventricular regions suggestive of small vessel disease.


No intra parenchymal bleed. No space occupying lesions or extra-axial collection.  Normal cerebellum and brainstem.  No bony destruction.

Summary

No acute haemorrhage. No significant changes to previous.

</record>
<record type="CT" order_item="CT Head With Contrast">
Clinical Details

Report

CT HEAD WITH CONTRAST:

Comparison made with the previous study.

The haematoma in the left fronto-parietal region appears smaller. There is still a considerable volume of fresh blood and surrounding oedema.  The degree of mass effect has decreased compared to previous scan.  Blood no longer visible within the ventricles.  The right-sided haematoma is no longer visible.

There are two MCA aneurysms which measure 7mm on the left and 8mm on the right. No visible surrounding blood.

No ring-enhancing lesions seen.

Opinion

Bilateral MCA aneurysms.

Resolving left intra axial haematoma.

No evidence of metastatic disease noted.

</record>
</records>
